workintelligent.ly 2016-05-19

# About Ricoh | Ricoh-USA

Ricoh USA, Inc. ("Ricoh") respects your online privacy and recognizes your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us. Ricoh has established this Privacy Policy so that you can understand how we intend to use and treat your Personal Information in the United States, and about the choices you can make in the way your information is collected and used. This policy does not cover the websites of Ricoh affiliates who publish their own policies. 

##  Changes to Ricoh's Privacy Policy

This Site and our business change constantly. As a result, at times it may be necessary for Ricoh to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Ricoh reserves the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice, and any changes will be effective immediately upon posting on this Site. Please review this Policy periodically, and especially before you provide any Personal Information. This Privacy Policy was last updated on September 18, 2015. Your continued use of the Site after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Policy. 

##  Types of Information we Collect - Personal Information

Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information. You may provide us with Personal Information in the course of ordering products or services, making requests, registering to receive materials or performing other activities. The types of Personal Information collected on these pages include such things as name, contact and billing information, transaction, and credit card information. If you are applying to a job at Ricoh, we may ask you to provide information such as educational background, employment experience, and job interest. 

In general, you can visit Ricoh’s web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself. If you choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you can still visit most of Ricoh’s Site, but you may be unable to access certain features, offers, and services that involve our interaction with you. 

When you do provide us with Personal Information, we usually use it to respond to your inquiry, process your order or provide you access to specific information, services or offers. If you chose to have a relationship with Ricoh, such as a contractual or other business relationship, we will naturally continue to contact you in connection with that business relationship including providing you with information about other Ricoh products and promotions that may be of interest to you. We (or a third party on our behalf) may contact you about a Ricoh offer in support of your business needs, to conduct surveys to better understand our customers' needs or for other purposes that Ricoh deems appropriate. 

##  Other Information

We may also collect non personal information including data about products and services that is not associated with a specific personal identity. For example, we may also ask you to provide us with information regarding your interests, demographics, and experiences with our products or services. Providing this additional information is optional. This information may be used to personalize our websites, services or communications and improve our products and services. We may also gather information about your usage of our website, such as pages visited, through the use of cookies or other automated technology such as web beacons. 

##  Use of Cookies

When you view one of our Sites, we, or one of our third party service providers, may store data on your device in the form of a "cookie" to automatically recognize your PC next time you visit. Cookies can help us in many ways, for example, by allowing us to tailor a Web site to better match your interests or to store your password to save you having to re-enter it each time. If you prefer not to receive cookies while browsing our Site, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser, although you may not be able to take full advantage of the Ricoh Site if you do so. 

##  Use of Information

In addition to the uses described above, Ricoh, like many businesses, sometimes hires other companies to help us deliver programs, products, information, and services. Examples may include mailing information, maintaining databases, filling an order, providing a service and processing payments. When we retain another non-affiliated company to perform a function of this nature, we seek to provide them with only the information that they need to perform their specific functions and we take reasonable steps to ensure that these third-party service providers are obligated to protect your Personal Information. 

Ricoh and its parent company, Ricoh Company Ltd of Japan, represent a global organization with legal entities, businesses, personnel, and technical systems that cross borders. We may share your Personal Information within the various Ricoh entities and transfer it to countries in the world where we do business. 

Circumstances may arise where, whether for strategic or other business reasons, Ricoh decides to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganize businesses in some countries. Such a transaction may involve the disclosure of Personal Information to prospective or actual purchasers, or receiving it from sellers. It is Ricoh’s practice to seek appropriate protection for information in these types of transactions. 

Except as provided in this Policy, Ricoh will not sell, rent or lease your Personal Information to any other third parties without your permission. Ricoh may, however, use your Personal Information to: (i) respond to duly authorized information requests of governmental authorities; (ii) comply with any law, regulation, subpoena, or court order or (iii) help prevent fraud or (iv) to enforce or protect the rights and properties of Ricoh or its affiliates. 

This site makes use of Google Analytics features, including remarketing and demographic reporting. We use this information to:

  * • help make the site easier for you to use
  * • help you find information, products, and services quickly
  * • help create and surface content that is most relevant to you
  * • alert you to new products and services that we offer 

If you would like to know more about how Google uses data generated from use of our sites, [click here for more information](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). If you would like to opt out of these features, you can do so by [installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). 

##  Accuracy & Access

Ricoh respects your desire that your Personal Information be accurately maintained. At your request, we will allow you access to your Personal Information so that you may view, update or correct it. To protect your privacy and security, we may take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access to your data. 

##  Security

Ricoh is committed to ensuring the security of your Personal Information. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. In certain areas of our Sites, Ricoh uses industry-standard 128-bit SSL-encryption in conjunction with firewalls to enhance the security of data transmissions. SSL encryption is designed to make the information unreadable by anyone but us. This security measure is working when you see either the symbol of an unbroken key or closed lock (depending on your browser) on the bottom of your browser window. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure the security of the information while it is in transit to us, and so we urge you to take every precaution to protect your Personal Information when you are on the Internet. We also suggest that you update your browser to the most current software/updates available, change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and after transactions close your browser to ensure that no data can be collected once you leave our Site. 

##  Children and Privacy

Ricoh does not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13 and Ricoh does not target the Site to children under 13. 

##  Linked Web Sites

Links to third party web sites from our pages are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave the Ricoh Site. RICOH HAS NOT REVIEWED ALL OF THESE THIRD PARTY SITES AND DOES NOT CONTROL NOR IS RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY OF THESE SITES, THEIR CONTENT OR THEIR PRIVACY POLICY. RICOH DOES NOT ENDORSE OR MAKE REPRESENTATIONS ABOUT THEM, OR ANY INFORMATION, PRODUCTS OR MATERIALS FOUND THERE, OR ANY RESULTS THAT MAY BE OBTAINED FROM USING THEM. IF YOU DECIDE TO ACCESS ANY OF THE THIRD PARTY SITES LINKED FROM THE RICOH SITE, YOU DO SO AT YOUR OWN RISK. 

##  How to Contact Us 

If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please mail your inquiry to Ricoh USA, Inc., 70 Valley Stream Parkway, Malvern, PA 19355, Attention: General Counsel.
